CI/CD compromise matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI, user identity,
clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Unsigned code matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI, user identity,
clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Insecure deserialization matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI,
user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Build pipeline attacks matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI,
user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Code signing Integrity validation Secure build pipelines Selected HIPAA mappings for this
topic include Section 164.312(c)(1) - Integrity;
Section 164.312(c)(2) - Mechanism to authenticate ePHI;
Section 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(B) - Risk management.